<resources>
    <string name="main_screen_activity_label">Main Screen</string>
    <string name="context_activity_label">Context</string>
    <string name="app_name">Wuhan_Guide_Helper</string>
    <string name="viewpoint_activity_label" />
    <string name="sunrise_at_lingbo_gate">Sunrise at Lingbo Gate</string>
    <string name="sunRiseAtLingboGateDescription">At Lingbo Gate, the sunrise paints the sky with hues of gold and crimson, casting a tranquil glow over the Yangtze River, where waves gently dance to the morning\'s first light.</string>
    <string name="yellow_crane_tower">Yellow Crane Tower</string>
    <string name="yellow_crane_tower_Description">The Yellow Crane Tower rises over Wuhan, a timeless sentinel, watching the Yangtze flow beneath golden eaves.</string>
    <string name="wuhan_university_sakura">Wuhan University Sakura</string>
    <string name="wuhan_university_sakura_Description">At Wuhan University, cherry blossoms bloom like delicate pink clouds, weaving a fleeting dream of spring across the ancient campus.</string>
    <string name="YellowCraneTowerIntroduction">The Yellow Crane Tower, perched on Snake Hill in Wuhan, is a historic and poetic landmark with over a thousand years of history. Its graceful design, featuring upturned eaves and intricate carvings, resembles a crane ready to take flight. Celebrated in classical Chinese poetry, the tower offers stunning views of the Yangtze River, inspiring awe in all who visit. A symbol of cultural heritage, the Yellow Crane Tower elegantly connects the past and present.</string>
    <string name="HotDryNoodles">Wuhan Hot Dry Noodles is a classic street food from Wuhan, China. Made with alkaline wheat noodles, it’s mixed with sesame paste, soy sauce, garlic, and chili oil, then topped with pickled radish and green onions. The noodles have a firm, chewy texture with a rich, nutty, and mildly spicy flavor.</string>
    <string name="WuDaIntroduction">Perched gracefully at the foot of Luojia Hill and kissed by the gentle waters of East Lake, Wuhan University stands as a timeless masterpiece, where history and nature intertwine. Founded in 1893, it is not only a cradle of knowledge but also a sanctuary of breathtaking beauty. Each spring, as the cherry blossoms awaken, the campus transforms into a living poem. Ancient halls and winding paths are adorned with clouds of pink and white, as petals drift softly on the breeze, weaving a dreamlike tapestry. Here, amidst the symphony of blooming trees and whispers of history, one finds not just a place of learning, but a haven of inspiration, where the fleeting charm of cherry blossoms invites hearts to wander and souls to reflect.</string>
    <string name="LinboGateIntrdouction">At the break of dawn, Lingbo Gate awakens, its serene waters mirroring the first blush of morning light. The horizon glows softly, as if painted by an artist\'s gentle hand, with hues of gold and crimson spilling over the tranquil surface of East Lake. Silhouettes of distant mountains stand like silent guardians, shrouded in a veil of mist, as the sun begins its ascent, casting long, shimmering rays across the rippling waters. The air is cool and crisp, carrying whispers of tranquility and renewal. Here, at this timeless gate where lake and sky embrace, the sunrise becomes a poetic moment, a quiet symphony of light and reflection that stirs the soul and lingers in memory.</string>
</resources>